Finding Aid for the Nancy Malone Papers PASC.0254
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Producing
  - unspecified
    - Like Mom, Like Me, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Photocopied and original clippings of reviews and ratings, and screening invitee list.
    - Like Mom, Like Me, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Like Mom, Like Me - photographs and contact sheets, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Like Mom, Like Me - script, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Script titled like Mother, Like Me. With one hard copy and soft bound published book.
    - Winner Take All, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Also known as Time Lock. Script and production information.
    - Winner Take All, 1975, 1981-1988 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Also known as Time Lock. Photographs, publicity, clippings, and distribution receipts.
    - Sherlock Holmes in New York, 1976, 1977, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Script, production material, publicity, photograph of Malone and John Huston signed by Huston.
    - Husbands and Wives, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Script material, production material, what appears to be Pitch-like presentation material and Twentieth Century Fox congratulatory certificate to Malone.
    - Sherlock Holmes in New York - end credits, no date (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Nurses (The) - photograph and Twentieth Century Fox certificate of commendation, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Winner Take All - end credits, 1975 Mar 5 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Like Mom Like Me, 1978 Nov 10, 1978 Oct 21, 1978 Nov 3, no date (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Letter from Greene to Malone, TV Guide issue 1334, photographs and clipping from Variety.
    - Five Finger Discount (The) -photographs and letter, 1977 Dec 19, no date (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Five Finger Discount (The) - clippings, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Five Finger Discount (The) - end credits, no date (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Community of Caring: Directors Guild of America - video, 1998 Mar 16 (Box 44)
      Label reads "DGA 1997 3/16/98 Dub from DBC trt 72.42. Santa Monica."
    - Lilac Productions Partner with Time Life, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      Contracts, articles of incorporation, shareholder minutes.
    - Lilac Productions Time Life Deal, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      Contracts and correspondence.
    - Lilac Productions, 1979 Jan-Feb (Box 47, Folder 4)
      Articles of incorporation, shareholders consent, bylaws, meeting minutes.
    - Caucus for Producers, Writers, and Directors (The), 1997-1998, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      Organization information, Spring 2000 journal issue, and October 1998 meeting minutes.
    - Womans Body by Nancy Malone and Linda Hope - idea for television, no date (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Speak Now or Forever - idea for television, no date (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Hottest Thing in Pants (The) by Nancy Malone and Linda Hope - first draft script, no date (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - 360 Park Avenue - idea, no date (Box 51, Folder 21)
      Removed from binder for preservation purposes.
    - Five-Finger Discount - mounted clipping, 1977 Nov (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Winner Take All - mounted clipping, 1975 Mar (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Teaching
  - unspecified
    - Directing Episodic Television (UCLA Extension), Winter 1993 and Spring 1998 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      Catalogue and snapshots.
    - Directing Episodic Television (UCLA Extension), 1992 June-1993 Apr (Box 47, Folder 8)
      Course material and employment forms.
    - Women in the Director's Chair (Banff Centre for the Arts), 1999 Aug-Dec, Jan 2000 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      Schedules, faculty employment forms and letters.
    - Acting for Television (Maria Piscator Institute), no date (Box 48, Folder 2)
      Clippings and brochure.
    - American Film Institute Master of Fine Arts informational brochure, 2005-2006 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Women in the Picture 2: Influence and Inspiration (Houston School of Film Galway, Ireland), 2006 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      Brochures and schedule.
    - Directing (W.I.F. Mentor Program Master Class) flier, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Guest lecture (Art Center College of Design Film Department) confirmation and bio, 2002 Sept (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Master Class with Nancy Malone (Stella Adler Academy) photocopied advertisement, 1995 Aug (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Senior Seminar and Acting Class in TV and Film (San Jose State University), 1984 May-Oct, 1985 Feb, 1985 Apr (Box 48, Folder 8)
      Correspondence, forms, newsletters, course materials, and clippings.
    - Nancy's UCLA Class - audio cassettes (13 items), 1993 Jan-Mar (Box 50)
      Restricted access.
    - Women in the Director's Chair Workshop (Banff Centre for the Arts) - videocassette, 2000 Jan (Box 50)
    - 3rd Women Filmmakers Symposium information, 1998-1999 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Women in Film
  - unspecified
    - Women in Film Foundation Agendas, 1999 May-2001 Feb (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Women in Film Foundation ByLaws 2000, 1999 Sep; 2000 Apr-Jul (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Women in Film Foundation Old ByLaws (See Section 21), no date (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Cash Flow (Cash Analysis), 1999 Apr-2000 Dec (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Women in Film Foundation Guidelines and "What We Do", ca. 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Women in Film Foundation Info Kit, 2000 Sep-Dec (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Contains copies of newspaper and journal articles ranging from 1998-2000.
    - Women in Film Foundation Info Kit (duplicate), 2000 Sep-Dec (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Women in Film Foundation Letters To Groups From Foundation, 2000 Mar (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Letter to Peg Yorkin regarding Feminist Expo 2000.
    - Women in Film Foundation Letters, Notices, Fax, Email, ca. 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Women in Film Foundation Meeting Notices, ca. 1998-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Women in Film Foundation Membership and Member Attendance, ca. 1996-1997; 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Women in Film Foundation Form Letter To New Members, Mar 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Women in Film Foundation Minutes, 1998-2001 Jan (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Women in Film Foundation Mission Statement, ca. 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Women in Film Foundation Nominating Committee (Nominations and Resignations), ca. 1994-1998; 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Women in Film Foundation Reel News: Monthly Letter From Foundation, 2000 Apr; 2001 Mar-Apr (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Women in Film Foundation Website (Donna Smith), 1999 Feb; 2000 Mar-May (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Women in Film Foundation Outreach: Women In Transition #1 (Tristine Rainer), 2000 Jun (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Women in Film Foundation Outreach: Women In Transition #2 (Judith Parker Harris), 2000 Sep (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Women in Film Foundation Outreach: Women In Transition #3 (Creating Your Financial Freedom), 2000 Dec (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Women in Film Foundation Outreach: Women In Transition #4 (Marilyn Barrett and Tony Bernay), 2001 Apr (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Women in Film Foundation Outreach: "Girls' Town" (Community Outreach), 1997 Sep-Nov (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Women in Film Foundation Outreach: Flash Forward "Reinventing Your Life", 1997 Oct (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Women in Film Foundation Outreach, 1999 Dec-2001 Apr (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Women in Film Foundation Retreat 1999, 1999 Aug-Oct (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Women in Film Foundation Retreat 1999 (Minutes and duplicates), 1999 Sep (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Women in Film Foundation Retreat 2000, ca. 2000 Nov (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Women in Film Foundation Miscellaneous Documents 1999, 1999 Jul (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Women in Film Foundation Miscellaneous Documents 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Women in Film Foundation Miscellaneous Documents 1992-1997, 1992 Feb; 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Women in Film Foundation Stationary and Envelopes, no date (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Women in Film Balance Sheets, 1998 Jul-1997 Aug (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Women in Film BOD Meetings, Agendas, Minutes, Reports, 1991 Jun; 1993 Oct; 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Women in Film Bylaws, 1992 Dec (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Women in Film Crystal Awards (23rd-24th), 1999 Jun; 2000 Jun (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Women in Film Fundraising: Auction at Cannes (2000), 2000 Mar (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Women in Film Hollace/Iris/Notices and Notes, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Women in Film International 2000 (and 1998 Directors Panel), 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Women in Film Lucy Awards (1 of 2), 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Women in Film Lucy Awards (2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Women in Film Martini Shot 1998 Program, 1998 Dec (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Women in Film Membership, 1999 Feb-2000 Mar (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Women in Film Miscellaneous (WIF Ads), no date (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Women in Film Mission Statement and BOD Mission Statement and Oath of Office, 1999 Dec; 2000 Apr (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Women in Film Personnel Policies, 1995 Sep (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Women in Film Pin, 1997 Nov-1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Women in Film Reel News and Miscellaneous WIF Calendars, 1997-2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Women in Film Strategic Planning Retreat 2000, 2000 Feb (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Women in Film Retreat 1999 (1 of 2), 1999-2000 Feb (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Women in Film Retreat 1999 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Women in Film's 25th Anniversary / DGA Seminar, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Bobbi Frank Resignation, 1998 Oct-2000 Nov (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Step Up WIF, 1998 Dec (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - BOD 2000 (WIF and WIFF): Evaluation Forms 2000, 2000 Jan-Aug (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Catering, 2000 May-Dec (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Committees and Proposals, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Corporate Overview (Use It As a Template), 2003 Apr (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Laser Pacific Signature Series (WIFF Project), 1994 Feb; 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Meta William's Complaint (Apr 7, 1998), 1998 Mar-Sep (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Mollie Gregory's Book, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Original Documents and Archival Materials (1 of 3), 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Original Documents and Archival Materials (2 of 3), 1973; 1977; 1997; 2001 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Original Documents and Archival Materials (3 of 3), no date (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Nancy's Miscellaneous Letters, 1993; 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Nancy's PSA, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Trade Rates For Ads (Variety etc.), 2000 May (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - NY WIF - Women's Film Preservation Fund, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - WIF 25th Anniversary Crystal Awards Luncheon Book, 2001 Jun (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Mollie Gregory Welles Book Project, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Women in Film Foundation Events and Grants, 1994 July-Aug, 1995 Feb-Mar (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Women in Film Foundation treasurers Reports and Fundraising guide, 1995 Mar-June, 1996 May (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Boardroom Babies Produced by Women in Film Version 1 / Version 2 - VHS tape, 1999 May (Box 6)
    - Ageism in the Entertainment Industry - KPFK Radio audio tape., 1998 Nov (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - DGA Summit - audio tapes (2 items), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Crystal Awards - Highlights Electronic Press Kit - VHS tape, 1998 Jul (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Women in Transition- VHS tape, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 1st Women in Film Awards Luncheon, 1977 June (Box 35, Folder 9)
      Mounted frame clipping.
    - Assorted papers, 1993 Oct (Box 44)
      Jerry's Deli Audio Tape Cable Show Removed from Box 57, folder 1.
    - Founders Award presented at the Lucy Awards, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      Speech, program, photographs and clippings.
    - Women in Film and L.A. Women's Foundation Fundraiser, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      Memos, notes, and program. Featuring Girl's Town screening.
    - Crystal Awards 21st Anniversary program, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Tichi Wilkerson Kassel Memorial program, 2004 March (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - 16th Annual Crystal Awards, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      Speech, program, photographs, and clippings.
    - Crystal Awards 20th Anniversary, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Event information, program, and speech notecards.
    - Women in Film - directories, 1974-1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - 1st Women in Film Awards Luncheon, 1977 June (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Invitation card and clippings. Mounted clipping moved to Box 35 folder 9 for preservation purposes.
    - Women In Film charter member Hall of Fame scroll, no year (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Women in Film Board of Directors list and clippings, 1973-2006 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Women in Film and Television International Summit ephemera and snapshots, 1998, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Reel News newsletters (2) and Variety clipping, 1997 Feb/Mar; 1998 June; 2000 May/June (Box 49, Folder 9)
      With a pamphlet titled The Status of Women On Screen and Behind The Camera in Entertainment TV (November 1990).
    - Women in Film Foundation meeting reminder, minutes and By-laws, 2001 Feb-Mar (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Crystal Awards program, 1996 (Box 50)
    - Crystal Awards program, 1995 (Box 50)
    - Women in Film general information and correspondence, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Women in Film/Women in Film Foundation Liaison, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      Board meeting minutes.
    - Women in Film Foundation meetings, agendas, and minutes, 1995 Mar-Apr, 1995 July, 1996 Oct-Dec (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Women in Film Executive Search Committee report, 1996 Oct-Dec, 1997 Mar-Apr (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Women in Film Finishing Fund, 1996-1998 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      Grants and awardees.
    - Women in Film - Macy's, 1997 Apr-May (Box 53, Folder 10)
      Outgoing fax memos.
    - Women in Film Crystal and Lucy Awards, 1997 Apr-July (Box 53, Folder 11)
      Fax memos and notes.
    - Women in Film Workshop, 1997 May, 1997 July (Box 53, Folder 12)
      Fax memos.
    - Women in Film budget and bylaws to be voted on December 16, 1992, 1992 Sept-Oct (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Crystals Logos, 1997 May-Aug (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - General Speeches - Nancy Malone, 1974-1976, 1993 Aug, 1996 Sept (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Assorted WIF Presentation packets, 1997-2004 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - International Summit 1998 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Assorted papers, 1996-1997 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      Mostly faxed memos related to Foundation.
    - Women in Film binder, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      Appears to be a handbook. Removed from binder for preservation purposes.
    - Women In Film and Television International Summit Los Angeles 1998 Resource Directory (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Cash Summary, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Assorted papers, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      Appears to be Women in Film Board of Directors meeting minutes. Removed Jerry's Deli Cable show cassette tape to Box 44.
    - Women in Film Reel News newsletters (16 items), 1992-1994 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Assorted papers, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      Appears to be Women in Film Board of Directors meeting minutes.
    - Women in Film binder, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Women in Film Crystal Awards program, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Women in Film 15th Anniversary Crystals program and Film Festival brochure, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Women in Film Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      WIFF Committee Operation guidelines, program descriptions, board/staff roles, and memo re. reorganization.